{"data":[{"question":"I couldn't catch the train. It _____.","a":"already left","b":"left already","c":"had already left","d":"has left already","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Past Perfect tense: \n+Expresses the idea that something occurred before another action in the past:\n Action \"already left\" lead to \" couldn't catch\"\n+ Structure: S+ had + already\/never\/ever ...+ PP+ (since\/for...)","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"14","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"He was annoyed. He _____ her all evening.","a":"has been phoning","b":"is been phoning","c":"phoned","d":"had been phoning","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Past Perfect Continuous:\n+Show that something started in the past and continued up until another time in the past; however, the duration does not continue until now, it stops before something else in the past.\n+ Structure: S+ had + (ever\/never...) been +V_ing+ (since\/for...)","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"14","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"When they arrived the film _____.","a":"had already begun","b":"has already begun","c":"had already began","d":"has already began","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Past Perfect tense: \n+ Expresses the idea that something occurred before another action in the past:\n Action \"begun\" happened before action \"arrived\"\n+ Structure: S+ had + (ever\/never...)+ PP+ (since\/for...)","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"14","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"We went on holiday to Portugal. We _____ there before.","a":"had never be","b":"have never been","c":"have never be","d":"had never been","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Past Perfect tense: \n+ Express the idea that something happened\/never happened before a specific time in the past\n+ Structure: S+ had + (ever\/never...)+ PP+ (since\/for...)","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"14","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"She found that the old man _____.","a":"has already left","b":"had already left","c":"had already leave","d":"has already leave","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Past Perfect tense: \n+Expresses the idea that something occurred before another action in the past:\n Action \"already left\"  happened before action \" found\"\n+ Structure: S+ had + already\/never\/ever ...+ PP+ (since\/for...)","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"14","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"When she arrived most of her friends _______.","a":"have left","b":"had left","c":"have leave","d":"had leave","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Past Perfect tense: \n+Expresses the idea that something occurred before another action in the past:\n Action \" left\"  happened before action \" arrived\"\n+ Structure: S+ had + (already\/never\/ever) ...+ PP+ (since\/for...)","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"14","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"She didn't recognise me. I _______ quite a lot.","a":"had changed","b":"have changed","c":"have change","d":"had change","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Past Perfect tense: \n+Expresses the idea that something occurred before another action in the past:\n Action \"changed\" lead to \" didn't recognised \"\n+ Structure: S+ had + (ever\/never...)+ PP+ (since\/for...)","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"14","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"She was tired. She _____ letters all day.","a":"has beeen typing","b":"typed","c":"had been typing","d":"is been typing","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Past Perfect Continuous:\n+Show that something started in the past and continued up until another time in the past; however, the duration does not continue until now, it stops before something else in the past.\n+ Structure: S+ had + (ever\/never...) been +V_ing+ (since\/for...)","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"14","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"He said that he _____ earlier.","a":"had come","b":"has come","c":"came","d":"is coming","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Past Perfect tense: \n+ Expresses the idea that something occurred before another action in the past: \n + Action \"come\" happened before action \" said\" \n+ Structure: S+ had + already\/never\/ever ...+ PP+ (since\/for...)","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"14","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"The teacher was late. He _____ late before.","a":"had never been","b":"had never be","c":"has never been","d":"has never be","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Past Perfect tense: \n+ Express the idea that something happened\/never happened before a specific time in the past\n+ Structure: S+ had + (ever\/never...)+ PP+ (since\/for...)","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"14","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"}]}